[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
How much farther
until we reach the end of this path?
We'll never get to the end
until the Sect Master is dead.
The Sect Master is a cunning man.
When you meet him, whether you will die or survive
depends half on heaven...
And half
on myself.
The Diamond Sutra says,
"no mark of self,
no mark of others,
no mark of living beings."
Make sure you decide
how you are going to
face the Sect Master.
[A Prophet]
[Episode 10]
Who exactly are you?
I am...
Shangguan Chengming.
Who gave you this name?
My...
My mother.
Mom...
I'm in so much pain.
It hurts badly.
Any disciples in Tianxiang Sect
[Eight years ago]
who leave without permission
shall be hunted down by the others.
Right, Junior?
I can guarantee
that after the two of you leave,
your whereabouts won't be known to anyone.
You've been gone for many years.
[Shangguan Hong]
Why did you come back?
Stop what you're doing.
Go with me.
Leave here for good.
There are rules in place.
Zhang Dancheng,
you've really gone every length
to take my position.
You feel better now?
Sir.
The...
the bleeding just won't stop.
Sir.
Sir!
She told me
that a stab wound in that spot
wouldn't cause death,
and that she could be saved.
She's already dead, sir.
Sir.
Sir,
have some tea.
Sit down.
What was on your mind, sir?
How do you think
Zhang Dancheng managed to find this boy?
Back then,
I went to the village where Hong lived
and asked many villagers.
They said Hong did have a child
who was studying away from home,
but nobody ever actually saw him.
Zhang Dancheng made me
kill the woman I loved most with my own hands.
Now,
he has my own son
bear the name of Wang Jiaxian
and come seek revenge against me in Tianxiang Sect.
He is trying to trick me
into killing my own son.
That's really
a dirty trick.
It's not dirty,
but vicious!
It takes several steps to kill him.
It's hard for you to find him,
but it's easy the other way around.
What should I do when I see him?
Just remember two sentences.
The first one:
A deadly blood feud.
Under no circumstances shall I change my name.
All my family members were killed by Tianxiang Sect.
Today, I failed to take revenge.
I only regret that I can't kill you with my own hands.
I found Wang Jiaxian's grave.
I dug it up
and saw bones inside.
If you are Wang Jiaxian,
then whose bones are those?
What's the second sentence?
It's as follows:
Shangguan Chengming.
This acupuncture technique will paralyze your whole body,
loosen your mind,
and make you speak the truth.
Maybe one day,
the Sect Master's Chief Batou,
Qin Baichuan,
will torture you
with needles.
When you feel like your soul has gone,
everything will be left to chance.
Who exactly are you?
I am...
Shangguan Chengming.
You're awake.
What's this place?
This is
where gofers live.
Here,
have some water first.
The Sect Master told me
to take good care of you.
See, how generous of the Sect Master.
You attempted to kill him,
yet he still treats you so well.
The Sect Master is done locking me up?
Let's grab a bite first.
I'm hungry.
Come on.
Careful.
Here.
Dig in.
Why don't you eat?
Buddy,
my mother once said,
difficulties will be all gone
when you fill your stomach.
If you don't eat, I will.
You can have the rest.
The vegetarian dishes here are awful.
Don't you look down on the cooks in Tianxiang Sect.
The food for us gofers is truly less than ideal.
But later,
the sect will hold a banquet.
When that happens, I'll show you
what delicacies are.
Delicacies?
Better save some room for them, right?
You wish.
You won't even get a seat at the main table.
I'm telling you,
all delicacies
are served to Batous only.
We only get to watch.
Watch?
What's the fun in that?
This showcases the brilliance of the Sect Master.
When gofers see Batous enjoying
such good stuff,
they'll naturally try their best to move their way up.
It's just a dinner.
Why take a photo?
This photo is to commemorate
Blind Du's downfall,
the Qian family's defeat,
and the fortune we raked in.
Usually, the sect
only holds a banquet
after accomplishing something huge.
Let's drink.
Sure.
Come on.
Liang.
Tell me.
Who are
these people?
Right now,
the one drinking a toast to the Sect Master
is Chief Batou, Qin Baichuan.
[Chief Batou, Qin Baichuan]
He's really nice to his subordinates.
But now, he's chief
of Muzilian Branch in Suhang.
So he rarely stays in Yucheng.
The man to the left of the Sect Master is the Second Batou.
The Sect Master
[The Second Batou, Porcelain Butcher]
took him in when he was little.
Much of the sect's dirty work
was done by him.
He's ruthless and brutal.
Before joining the sect,
he even snatched buns from starving people.
He gets really excited at the sight of dead bodies.
Currently,
he's running a coffin shop.
Oh, right.
There's one more thing.
Though he never says it to anyone,
it's known to everybody
that he's very much into the Fifth Batou.
Yanzi.
To the right
of the Sect Master,
the man in glasses
is the Third Batou.
He's literate.
[The Third Batou, Needle in Cotton]
He smiles at everyone.
Every time he smiles at me,
it gives me the creeps
and unsettles my nerves.
He's closest to the Seventh Batou,
who is seated next to him,
with a fair powdered face.
He used to be an opera singer
[The Seventh Batou, Immortal's Hand]
playing female roles.
He knows a bit of sleight of hand.
So he's nicknamed
the Immortal's Hand.
He is junior
to all the other Batous.
But he's particularly good at reading people's faces.
That's how he weaseled his way in with the Third Batou.
As for the Fourth Batou,
he learns from Westerners.
[The Fourth Batou, Zhang Zizhan]
He's of different origins from ours.
He rarely designs scams.
But the Sect Master
values talent,
so he keeps him close.
The woman beside him,
Huang Farong,
[Huang Farong, from Yuehaitang Branch]
is his wife.
She works for Yuehaitang Branch.
Then the man in sunglasses
must be the Sixth Batou, right?
[The Sixth Batou, Master Swindler]
He's nicknamed the Master Swindler.
I guess he's the best fighter in our sect.
Besides, he's really close
to the Sect Master.
He's always with the Sect Master
when the latter's out pulling scams.
Word has it in the sect
that he will be
the Sect Master's successor.
He's nothing but a lackey of the Sect Master's.
I know you hate the Sect Master.
I don't know why the Sect Master keeps you around,
but I'm sure you're not the first one who attempted to kill him.
There was a time
when the Six Batou nearly took his life.
[Linjiang Pier]
[Eighteen years ago]
He's the great master you talked about?
Yes, exactly.
Previously, there was a severe drought.
The river stopped yielding fish.
But ever since he arrived,
the fish have been jumping out
of the water like crazy.
Now, the fishermen
all rush to offer him money.
For that, we're losing our cut.
Fish!
Look, so many fish!
Why do fish
obey him like that?
The Sect Master had a secret recipe.
He took green-shelled eggs from silkie hens,
marinated them with mutton for seven days and seven nights,
then added yellow azalea and sleeping powder,
and finally made it into fish bait.
The fish would come as they smelled the fishy scent.
After taking the bait, they got drunk
and stayed motionless,
so people could easily catch them.
These damn frauds!
How dare they humiliate me on my turf.
Whoever takes him out
can get 10 percent
of our future cuts.
Boss,
these people are from Tianxiang Sect.
They are not to be trifled with.
No one in the underworld is to be trifled with!
Are you just going to let them walk all over us?
Boss.
I'll take him down.
Only those who stand shoulder to shoulder
can be called brothers.
If you make it,
I guarantee you wealth and glory.
Sect Master,
let me handle him.
If you die,
I'll take care of your family.
I will treat
your mother as my own.
If you want to kill me, just get it over with.
You risked your life
for a few words your boss said.
You do have some guts.
But are you sure your boss,
the Sea Overlord, is a real man?
Don't you know the terrible things
he did to the villagers?
To lose your life for man like that...
You're such a fool.
Am I supposed to believe you over him?
You don't have to believe me.
Let me wait with you for the result.
Take him away.
What an interesting way of holding nails.
It's just as interesting as you are.
You...
The Sect Master
locked him up for about a month.
The Sixth Batou
finally calmed down.
But when he returned home,
he found his mother had starved to death.
Later, people started moving things out of his house.
Only then did he realize
that the Sea Overlord had even sold his house.
It was the Sect Master who paid to hold
a proper funeral for his mother.
The Sixth Batou
is quite a filial son.
He visits his mother's grave every year.
Some time later,
he killed the Sea Overlord on his own.
Afterwards, he joined the sect
and became loyal to the Sect Master.
Buddy,
the Sect Master is actually quite nice.
He's really not what you think.
Look, I've been in the sect for years.
I've heard and seen
quite a lot.
To my knowledge, the Sect Master has never ordered to kill.
Look at this flower.
Pretty red, isn't it?
But in your eyes, it looks black.
Why?
You're only seeing
what's on the surface.
My own experience must be real then, right?
I...
I lost all my family and then
came to this town
to make a living.
You didn't slack off?
Big Teapot!
I poured tea for people in a teahouse.
Everyone called me Big Teapot.
He really looks like a big teapot.
Sir,
sorry for the kerfuffle.
Everyone,
my apologies.
Enjoy yourselves.
Take your time and enjoy.
There you are, sir.
What happened to your face?
Nothing.
Put your hand down.
Turn your face around.
You're badly hurt.
This time, for what?
I accidentally
broke a customer's item yesterday.
I deserved the beating.
Enjoy yourself, sir.
Wait.
This is my address.
If you're done with being beaten here every day,
then come find me.
By the way...
Can you read?
No, I can't.
Then have the note read to you.
Get me the check!
Yes, sir!
Three copper coins.
The next day,
I made up my mind
and went to that address
to meet with the Sect Master.
Silly Liang!
Yes, Sect Master.
You made contributions too.
Care to join us for a drink?
No,
Sect Master.
I'm not fit to sit at that table.
Enjoy yourself, Sect Master.
What a kid.
Oh my, that was quite a fright.
Everyone, let's call it a day.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Must be those vile creatures from the Plum Blossom Sect again.
They've been pulling stunts everywhere lately,
cooking up some sort of crap miracle
and stealing much of our business.
What miracle?
The ascension of immortal children.
Immortal child, please get on the heavenly ladder.
Look, the immortal child is ascending to the sky!
The immortal child is ascending to the sky!
Thank you, Master!
The merits are accomplished.
You will be relieved of three sufferings.
Blessings shall extend to you and your kin.
The plum blossoms open the holy path!
Liang,
is it really that mystical?
Could you take me there for a look?
No way.
The Sect Master said
that you must stay strictly within Tianxiang Sect.
I know how to break up this scam.
Come on, give it a rest.
Even these many Batous can't figure a way.
What makes you think you can?
Liang,
when you first saw them casting the ritual,
was it around the first day of the lunar month?
How did you know that?
Think about it.
There were barely any stars
in the sky that night, right?
Yes, exactly.
If we solve this difficulty, you'll be
deemed to have made a major contribution by the Sect Master.
Perhaps by then,
I'll even have to call you
grandmaster.
I'd like to hear you say it now.
Not before we get the job done.
Buddy,
thank you for helping me.
Let me treat you to candied haws.
One bite for me.
One bite for you.
If I do become a Batou
when this is done,
I'll treat you to meat.
Still, one bite for me,
and one bite for you.
Come on, have a bite.
One handcuff for you and one for me as well, huh?
I have my cut, and you have yours.
Fine then.
The one performing the ritual
should be Mei Xuanzi, head of the Plum Blossom Sect.
Behold,
the immortal child is to ascend the heavenly ladder.
How insolent!
Who are you devil creature
to stop the immortal child's ascension?
Take him down!
Move aside!
Move!
Get down here!
Come down right now!
Leave the ladder!
There was a balloon attached.
You have all been deceived.
They drug the children
and tie them to a balloon
with a black thread while they are unconscious.
As the children climb up,
the balloon will carry them high in the sky
only for them to fall to their deaths.
My little boy!
What is this about?
We will take the money.
By the code of this line of work,
he who wrecks my setup
must have his tongue cut out
and be expelled from the sect he's in.
Sect Master,
will you do it, or shall my men do it?
Master Mei, this is not right.
Laying down rules
at my own place...
It's inappropriate, isn't it?
Let me tell you
the rules of Tianxiang Sect.
Subjecting the people to suffering,
separating families,
and harming children
are not to be tolerated.
Is this your stance
on this matter, Sect Master?
Today, you must hand this person over,
or I'll turn the entire Tianxiang Sect
upside down!
I don't believe it.
Let me see which of you dares to make a move.
You.
Who else?
Stop playing tricks.
And you.
Oh, that broken chair of mine.
It caused you to fall.
Come on.
Get up now.
Let me see.
Are you alright?
Anything else you'd like to say?
Sect Master,
our paths will cross again.
We'll have plenty of time to settle this.
Goodbye and take care. I won't see you out.
Sir.
Stop watching.
Come out here, you two.
The two of you did put on quite a show.
The Plum Blossom Sect has been completely humiliated.
Rescuing the innocent
and helping families reunite...
That's a good deed.
You deserve rewards.
That said, in Tianxiang Sect, the code
has always been to reward merit and punish fault without ambiguity.
Rewards and punishments
will be given fairly.
Is it correct, Silly Liang?
Yes.
Sect Master, I know I did wrong.
What did you do wrong?
I left my post without permission.
I also took the liberty
of letting Shangguan Chengming out of the sect.
I disobeyed your orders, Sect Master.
What should we do with you then?
You have to be punished, right?
Sir, I'm truly sorry for what I did.
I won't take the gold.
I only beg you for a chance to make things right.
Please spare my life, sir.
You were always eager to foil the Plum Blossom Sect's scheme.
Liang's doing actually
brought honor to Tianxiang Sect, right?
Besides,
I came back here already, didn't I?
You do have a point.
Tell you what?
I'll do Chengming a favor.
Get up, Liang.
Thank you, sir.
I'll also give you
a chance to mend your ways.
The Plum Blossom Sect
has been in the limelight lately.
I can't just sit back and watch.
I plan to hold a ceremony
and make it a big one,
so as to let the whole world know
that Tianxiang Sect reigns supreme.
I now trust you
with this task.
Sir, I'm sorry for what I did.
Sir,
I-I-I am really not up for the task.
Look at you, having no ambition at all.
It's just a ceremony, isn't it?
Liang.
I'll help you.
You lot have caused quite a stir this time.
Those children's parents
are now complaining to the police station.
We will compensate those families.
Director,
could you please do us a favor
and let this one slide?
Do people in the Plum Blossom Sect
only buy one shoe at a time?
I got it. I got it.
It takes a group to form a gang.
Good things should come in pairs.
Here is
the other shoe.
That's more like it.
Who in Yucheng doesn't know how hard
you've worked and how much you've contributed, Director Fan?
You're holding up half
of the city by yourself, Director Fan.
This time, Tianxiang Sect
humiliated us in front of many
and made us suffer a great loss.
If you could kindly help us—
You want to get even?
Tianxiang Sect is powerful and has many disciples.
They are not to be messed with.
Man schemes a thousand ways,
but Heaven has the final say.
From now on, 80% of the Plum Blossom Sect's profits
will be yours.
Well then...
wait to hear from me.
Sure.
Director,
don't forget about the stuff.
As a public servant,
I stay clear of gold and silver.
You just pay for the tea today.
Director,
the Plum Blossom Sect case is closed.
They'd like to offer you
a token of appreciation.
Is this all?
This is all of the gift.
I had a meeting with the superiors today.
They want me to be the deputy corps commander.
I will highly recommend you to them,
so you can
take over my position.
Director,
please spare me all this testing.
They're transferring you
only to put their own people in.
I swear to God that I've never
thought about taking your position.
It is my greatest blessing
to be your subordinate all my life.
That post of deputy corps commander is just a figurehead.
It sounds like a promotion in rank,
but it comes with little real power.
But if I refuse it,
I might not get
a better chance in the future.
I really have no idea
if this is a blessing or a curse.
Director,
don't fret.
How about asking a master to tell your fortune?
I'd love to do some divination.
But
there are too few real masters nowadays.
Meanwhile,
frauds prevail.
That's right.
Director,
There is an amazing fortune teller in Yucheng,
famous throughout the southwest.
Do you know him?
I haven't had any dealings with him,
but I can find him.
If he dares to scam you...
I'll finish him off
before you even lift a finger.
Alright then.
Sir.
How do I look?
Great.
They were made in America.
So classy.
I called for you.
What took you so long?
I got up early
to visit my mother's grave.
I was too busy before
to have time for that.
Did you say how you've been at your mother's grave?
Yes, I did.
I had you come over just to ask you
how Shangguan Chengming is doing lately.
You've really
sent him on an impossible mission.
He's not even a member of our sect.
No one listens to him.
That's good.
Only in this way will he figure out his position.
Sir, you've put a lot of thought into this,
but I doubt
if this kid will
understand your intentions.
Let things take their course.
Sit.
I'd like to take this chance
to report something to you.
We've got a new job.
Director Wang of the police bureau seems
to have been given a chance at promotion.
He would like to invite you over
to tell his fortune, probably.
You mean Wang...
Wang Zhicheng?
Yes.
Haven't you always wanted to befriend him?
I think this is a great opportunity.
Here is all the information about him.
Did you get this?
Fan Jialie gave it to me.
Director Wang also had him send the invitation to you.
I think...
Hold on.
Something's not right.
Shortly after we ruined the Plum Blossom Sect's setup,
Fan Jialie...
Could this...
be a trap?
Every year, our sect
has never been short a single cent
of the money for Fan Jialie.
This matter is not that simple.
Then how about...
I turn this down?
Why would we turn away a business opportunity
delivered right to our door?
[Shunxiang Teahouse]
You achieved success
at 29, Director Wang.
That was because you nearly
lost your life at 28.
So, surviving a great disaster actually
brings good fortune, right?
You are destined to be with three women.
That's true.
I just recently
took a third woman.
Congratulations.
Anything wrong?
This promotion is an obstacle in your career.
You might lose your official post next year.
Astrologically speaking,
your prospects are vast.
But the obstacle next year
is likely related to feng shui.
May I ask
if your residence is next to waters and trees?
Shouldn't that be good feng shui?
It should be.
But I'm afraid the big trees might be
blocking the waters before the doors and windows.
As the ancients said,
a single leaf can obscure the view.
For ordinary folks, it's no big deal
for trees to cast their shade on the river.
But for you, Director Wang,
a man with vast prospects,
that's a hindrance.
Don't worry, though.,
I'll adjust the feng shui for you.
You truly are a master, sir.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please accept this.
Sir,
why don't you take the money?
It's an honor to be of your service, Director Wang.
How can I take your money?
I'm leaving.
Guards!
What's this supposed to mean?
You're not much
of a good fortune teller, are you?
Every word you said was pure nonsense.
Director Wang,
he's just a charlatan,
a big fraud!
Take him down!
To distinguish right from wrong is wisdom;
to invert them is folly.
Put it in a way I can understand.
Fine.
I'll do three final readings for you.
Great then.
Proceed right now.
If the results turn out to be accurate,
I'll let you go.
But if not,
I'll shoot you dead
on the spot!
[In the next episode]
I'll deal with him sooner or later.
[The show begins]
He's still too young.
How is the preparation for the ritual
to lead the dead to rebirth going?
Set up the alter.
Liang,
can we skip it today?
It's an important task. I must take it head on.
I'm afraid the Plum Blossom Sect will come mess with us.
If you're fear death, go home and raise pigs.
May my son
be healthy
and live a life free of illness.
Liang.
No way.